Guess what. uncle Crowley?
I'm hungry.
Sam: So. Amara's growing like
a radioactive weed?
Dean: By stuffing her face
with souls.
Crowley: If she's half
as powerful as I think she is.
I want her on my team.
The Darkness is almost
infinite power.
We're bound. Dean.
God kicked this thing's ass
once before.
We need your help. God.
You know who we need
to help deal with
the Darkness.
Hello. Demon Tablet.
He was God's scribe.
He did hear about everything.
Dean: Detective Madsen.
I saw a guy hanging around earlier.
That's Len.
I think Amara
sucked out his soul.
I'll confess
to all the murders.
Holy crap.
That way. I can't get out.
We can't kill him 'cause
he hasn't done anything yet.
Dean.
we don't want to kill him.
We want to save people.
[ Snaps fingers ]
Right. your new rules.
What can I do to help?
Sam: No. no. no.
you just. uh. sit there.
take a breather.
Watch some Netflix.
Okay.
Dean: Besides.
we got bigger fish to fry.
Bye. Dean.
I'll see you soon.
[ Goldie laughs ]
So. she says dating's gonna
break my focus for academics.
but that I'm allowed to date
over summer break.
How does that work?
Like. "Hi. I'm Goldie.
I'm only romantically available
from June to August.
but want to go steady?"
[ Laughs ]
I hate her.
Like. look at me.
I have to hang out by the tracks
just to get my snack on.
She won't let you
eat chips?
Well. she'll let me.
but just so she can make
this face the whole time.
[ Cellphone chimes ]
[ Laughs ]
It's like. "Sorry. mom.
I can't survive on menthol
and diet soda like you can."
Oh.
What? No.
Look. I hate my parents. too.
Goldie. They suck.
But I got a curfew.
Bye.
Fine.
Whoa.
Hey.
Where are your parents?
I don't have any parents.
Sorry. Um...
Are you okay?
Do you want something?
I want to be like you.
[ Whooshing ]
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
[ Clicks ]
[ Sighs ]
Midnight snack?
Don't think I don't know
what you've been up to.
You can try to deny it.
but the evidence is...
Well.
You told me to stop
feeding on your demons.
Well...
I stopped feeding on demons.
I thought I was clear.
Going out there.
where they can see you --
it's too risky.
I'm a growing girl.
I need to eat.
Actions have consequences
around here. Amara.
You've had the run
of the court.
We've seen
what you've made of it.
Believe me.
this is going to hurt me
way more
than it hurts you.
I'm sorry. my dear.
You're grounded.
[ Whooshing ]
You're strong.
But you need to remember --
I'm stronger.
For now.
Yeah.
♪ Supernatural 11x06 ♪
Our Little World
Original Air Date on November 11. 2015
== sync. corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Said you had a good feeling
about that one.
Yeah. well. it seemed like
a solid lead. Dean.
Only a soulless psycho
would kill the family cat.
Yeah.
unless the family cat
decides to take a nap
in the dryer.
You know.
we've been here since Monday
and still haven't found
another legit victim.
Maybe Amara moved on
or stopped feeding altogether.
Well...
finding her victims
is still the best shot we got
at finding her.
Not actually true.
Oh. what?
You think he's ready?
He's had a pretty rough go of it
lately.
Which one of us hasn't?
Seems insane to leave our one and
only angel friend on the bench.
I'll call him.
Thank you.
[ Dialing ]
Man: ...It literally
doesn't matter.
[ Cellphone ringing ] Jones: Well. we're
gonna get to all the results
in just a second.
We're gonna start with. uh...
Let's go back
to our first story.
Uh. Louis. Silla. and Edwin.
Hi.
Cass.
How you doing. buddy?
We did a DNA test on Louis.
Oh. I'm fine.
Find anything
on Metatron?
Um. nothing on angel radio.
How long's it been
since you left the bunker?
Oh. why would I leave?
I've got everything I need
right here.
Wait. Is that --
are you watching
"Jenny Jones"?
It's a rerun.
She's just about to announce
the paternity results.
You are the father.
[ Cheers and applause ]
Jenny. he is not ready
to be a father.
Okay.
I-I-I thought you were going
with socially acceptable
binge watching.
Uh. you know. "The Wire."
"Game of Thrones."
Yeah. well. a man can't live
on caviar alone. Dean.
Well. you sound weird.
okay?
[ Cellphone rings ]
Bad weird.
Now. I've been
down this road before.
What's up. Detective?
I have heard the siren's song
from the idiot box.
and I'm telling you.
whatever you're looking for.
you won't find it
in there.
So do me a favor.
Oh.
Turn off the TV.
Go outside and get some air.
We're in the dark here.
pal.
I need you back in the game.
okay?
[ Sighs ]
[ Click ]
I get it.
Yeah. well.
thanks for letting me know.
We'll -- we'll head out there
right now.
You got it.
What's up?
Sam: That was Detective Madsen.
Remember our friend Len?
Uh. weird as hell.
soulless.
took-the-rap-for-all-the-murders
Len?
Yeah.
He's dead.
[ Engine turns over ]
Dean:
[ Echoing ] Cass! Cass!
Don't do this.
[ Grunts ]
Okay. this isn't you.
It's the spell.
You can beat this.
[ Grunting ]
Efram: I will end you!
No!
[ Growls ]
Don't!
Castiel: I won't let you
walk out of this room.
[ Both grunting ]
Marco got one of them
last night --
a Len Fletcher?
Tell Marco
to keep looking.
The last thing I need is
one of Amara's candy wrappers
blabbing to angels
or hunters
about what.
who happened to them.
Where is everyone?
Oh. our ranks
have been a bit thin
since Amara
ate everybody.
I've got some fresh numbers
for you to go over before court.
Soul projections --
they're not good.
We're down for the quarter.
which means that...
That door was supposed
to be locked and guarded 24/7.
Of course. sir.
I don't see a guard.
Uh. right.
Must be a mix-up.
We're short-staffed and all.
so...
Congratulations.
You've been demoted.
No one goes in or out
of that room.
[ Buzzer ]
Thought maybe a relative
of one of Len's victims.
but it doesn't feel
like a revenge killing.
Too clean.
like an assassination.
Man: Detective.
Excuse me.
You smell that?
Yeah.
Yeah. either the detective needs
to change his diet or. uh --
Sulfur.
Len was killed by a demon.
Yeah. but why would a demon
order a hit on a guy with no soul?
It's like a Cracker Jack
but not a prize.
Hands off. Deputy Doody!
[ Grunts ]
Who's the girl?
Goldie Schmidtlapp.
Was a normal kid.
snapped this morning --
tried to kill her mom
with a frying pan.
First the ax murders. then Len.
now this?
We're gonna need
to talk to the kid.
Man: That's four legs
on four wheels.
[ Dog barks ]
[ Chuckles ] Ah. that dog
thinks it's people.
Up next. a very upsetting story
out of Omaha.
A downtown bar fight escalated
tragically last night.
And "OWW2 news"
brings you an exclusive video
of the event.
The footage you're about
to view is extremely graphic.
[ Both grunting ]
[ Indistinct shouting ]
[ Gunshot ]
[ Woman screams ]
Efforts were made
to resuscitate the victim.
but unfor--
[ woman screams ]
♪
[ Cell door closes ]
Goldie: Hey. officer. I still
haven't gotten my phone call.
Do you think I could get
a pizza delivered in here?
You're not the deputy.
Nope.
[ Sighs ]
Boss' daughter's been
making a mess in town.
and it's my job
to clean it up.
Nothing personal.
Nice work. Goldie.
So. Crowley and Amara?
Huh.
Dean:
Rise and shine. buttercup.
Now...about
what you were saying.
What's Crowley doing
with Amara?
Don't know. don't care.
Wouldn't tell you
if I did.
Hmm.
Well. we already know
she's growing up fast.
Yeah. well. demon souls --
they do a body good.
[ Sighs ]
Little Muppet tore
through half my buds
before Crowley put her
on a diet.
She didn't like that.
Started sneaking out
to get her fill.
You know how kids are.
But daddy
put his foot down.
Where's he hiding her?
[ Chuckles ]
I'm happy to keep gossiping
with you boys.
but you want
actionable intelligence?
Torture me if you want.
I know you'll just kill me
anyway.
Hmm.
Well. it looks like
a stalemate to me.
I guess we go ahead
and kill him right now.
No. no. no.
Dean. wait.
We can exorcise him.
What?
Save his meat suit.
My two cents?
You exorcise me.
let me smoke on out of here.
I give you my word
not to tell Crowley.
[ Scoffs ]
[ Chuckles ]
Hey. you heard me.
He's hardly my favorite guy
at the moment. I --
Wait a second.
Shut up.
Well.
would you look at that.
There's no way his suit
survived that wound.
Mnh-mnh.
All right.
Crap.
[ Crackling ]
Aah!
[ Door opens ]
Hey.
Where'd you
ditch the body?
School playground.
Come on.
Hospital parking lot.
What do you got?
Well. uh. good news.
I was able to hack his phone.
Got the coordinates
of his call history.
I guess Crowley must've had him
tailing Amara or something.
'cause he was at
all three spots.
He was at
the Lizzie Borden house.
where Len
got his soul taken.
he was at the bar where Sydney got
her soul taken. and he was here.
where Goldie said Amara
approached her.
Hmm.
So. somewhere in there.
Yeah. maybe.
But what I don't get is.
why would Crowley have Amara
on earth in the first place?
Wouldn't it be smarter
to -- to keep her in Hell?
Yeah. but then he'd have
to spend more time there.
and he hates that place.
Oh. right.
[ Chuckles ]
I keep forgetting about you
and Crowley's summer of love.
I'm not seeing much inside this
radius that he'd like better.
I mean. you got farms. you got swamps.
Yeah.
This P.O.I.. what's that?
Uh...
Point of interest.
I know what it --
what is it?
Oh. Let's find out.
Yeah.
[ Keyboard clacking ]
The Needham Asylum.
Decommissioned in '63.
Sound like Crowley's
kind of place to you?
♪
[ Door closes ]
Crowley:
What are you looking at?
Still learning all you can
about the world?
If nonsensical slogans
attached to idiotic pictures
of domestic animals
counts as the world.
Excuse me?
Memes.
Ah.
Look. I know to you
my rules seem...
Unfair. arbitrary.
as though I'm doing all this
just to hurt you.
I don't care
why you do anything.
I just want you to know
that I'm not a monster.
Jervis?
I can't have you
eating whatever. whenever.
however much you want.
I thought you might appreciate
a little snack.
I'm not hungry.
[ Grunting ]
I'll leave you
to your memes.
[ Sighs ]
I have no idea
what I'm doing here --
not a bleeding clue.
Moment to moment.
what makes you happy?
What will set you off?
How do I even begin
to forge a connection with you?
But what I do know is
you're growing so fast.
and it terrifies me.
I bet.
You only want me
for the power I'll wield.
and you know. soon enough.
I won't need you anymore.
Sam: So. we're really
gonna do this...
Now?
Hell. yeah.
I've been looking for a chance
to get back at Crowley
ever since that crap he pulled
in Cedar Rapids.
especially now that I know
he tricked me
and made off
with the Darkness.
No.
that's not what I meant.
We're going in
to kill Amara.
Are you ready for that?
Why wouldn't I be?
Because we don't know
the first thing about her. Dean.
We don't know her powers.
We don't know
how to take her down.
Hell. you know what?
We don't even know
if she can be killed.
I know.
But she's too big of a threat
to wait.
I say we go in there
and we hit her
with everything we got.
[ Sighs ]
Crowley:
You have tremendous power.
and soon
you'll have even more.
But I have something
you lack...
Wisdom. experience.
I helped put Lucifer back
in his cage.
I rose
through the ranks of Hell.
defeated all comers.
to claim the throne.
And. a few minor setbacks aside.
I'm still here.
I don't know how to impart
what I've learned to you.
how to teach you.
And at the rate
that you're growing.
I'll probably never get
the chance to figure it out.
[ Sighs ]
Perhaps you don't need
my tutelage.
But I believe.
deep down in my gut.
I have something
to offer you
if you'd just give me
the chance.
What are you asking for?
Time.
Slow down.
Play by my rules
for just a little bit longer.
You give me
your patience.
I'll give you
my protection...
...until you decide
you don't need it anymore.
Okay.
[ Car alarm wailing
in distance ]
Metatron: Oh. this is good.
A night-leader
if ever I saw one.
And this is gonna fetch me $500.
minimum.
I. uh -- I know that
$500 sounds like plenty.
but with my overhead...
[ Sighs ]
...daddy's got to eat.
[ Coughs ]
Oh. come on!
[ Choking ] Help.
Please.
[ Scoffs ]
I'm sorry. buddy.
Y-you live. there's no story.
[ Choking ]
[ Groans ]
You know.
there was a time
I could have brought you
back from the brink
with a snap
of my fingers...
Not that I would have.
But I'm not that guy
anymore.
I can't save you.
I can.
How did you find me?
Same way you found him.
Scoured
the police scanners.
got ahead
of the authorities.
[ Whooshing ]
[ Groaning ]
[ Breathing heavily ]
What was that?
What?
Look. a real-life angel
caught on tape?
That is way better
than some random homicide.
Hey!
Do you have any idea
how much stuff I had to steal
and then pawn
to pay for that?!
[ Siren chirps ]
[ Gate rattles ]
No guards
at the perimeter?
Sam: Looks like there are
no guards at the door. either.
You think this is
the right place still?
Well...warding sigils.
And for the humans --
look at this.
A padlock you'd find
on a middle-school locker.
Cocky son of a bitch.
Dean.
external security may be lax.
but we still don't know
how many demons
we're gonna face inside.
Well. let's find out.
[ Lock disengages ]
[ Door creaks ]
Turn to the graph
at the bottom of 27.
and you'll see
a nearly 40% decrease
in soul collections
in the Pacific Northwest
over the past three years.
An unexpected consequence
of legalized marijuana?
Some analysts think so.
Others are not quite so sure.
Aah!
Oh!
Okay. "Marv"...
You're picking pockets.
leaving a man to die.
I-I -- I don't know
what I expected.
but this
is disappointing.
One to talk.
You chose
the life of a wage slave.
slinging slurpees
for. what. a month?
I am in it to win it.
I was at zero
when you took my Grace.
hiding from angels.
not a cent to my name.
But I found my calling.
and I pulled myself up
by my bootstraps
and started a business.
And. you know.
my story has only just begun.
What story is that?
You're preying like a vulture
on human tragedy.
Oh! [ Chuckles ]
Castiel!
[ Chuckles ]
What century are you in?
Religion is dead!
The novel? Deader.
You think I'm ashamed
for dealing in
fleeting visual sensation.
in gift-length glimpses of
horror. waste. and degradation?!
No!
I just caught up
with the times.
Reality is the great literature
of our era.
and I am out there.
on the streets.
every single night.
capturing it!
I am reality's author.
Oh. save your story.
It is not what I came for.
Oh.
So...
Straight to business.
You want
the Demon Tablet?
Well.
you're not gonna get it.
I have hidden it
very carefully
in a place
where you and your friends --
You hid it
under your mattress.
The TV station
gave me your address.
and I-I checked
the place out.
You realize
you have bedbugs?
You broke into
my apartment?
What do you know
about the Darkness?
The band?
Okay.
Uh...Sometimes during
late-night writing sessions.
when God was
deep in his cups.
he may have let slip
a few choice words.
But...
I don't have
to tell you anything.
Are you forgetting?
[ Gasps ]
[ Grunts ]
You are human now. and I could
crush you like a bug.
Could. but you won't.
You think
I didn't notice?
You are broken. Castiel.
You were always
a bit of a Nancy. but this?
[ Sighs ]
You have gone full wuss.
I don't know what it was
that happened.
but whatever it was.
you are scarred...deep.
paralyzed by trauma.
by fear.
[ Laughs ]
I mean. look at you.
You can't even hit me!
Oh!
It's not fear.
Aah!
Crowley:
Hey. idiot. andale --
Spanish for
"get your ass over here."
You think I've been paying
your astronomical bar tabs...
Sir?
...for the past five weeks
so you can sleep past noon
with last night's skank?
Well. Dean?
[ Grunting. punches landing ]
Sam?
[ Handcuffs clicking ]
[ Man speaking
indistinctly ]
You know what? Go.
Take her out.
I got them.
♪
I knew you'd come.
I'm sorry. Amara.
For what?
What I have to do.
Hello. Dean.
[ Whooshing ]
My girl's growing up.
Should have known
it wouldn't be long
before the boys came
sniffing around.
[ Dean grunts ]
[ Whooshes ]
Aah!
[ Grunts ]
What do you want with her.
Crowley?
What. you think you can use her.
control her?
You're an idiot.
I'm not trying
to control her.
[ Knife clatters ]
I'm helping her
to realize
her fullest potential.
Do you know
how disturbing it was
to realize that I couldn't
bring myself to kill you?
I've had tons of chances
over the years.
some you don't even know about.
but. still...
I made my peace with it.
embraced my softer side.
learned to accept that there
was just too much going on
between you and I --
bromance.
But you know what?
I think I am
gonna kill you today.
I feel different somehow.
ready.
What can I say?
Fatherhood changes a man.
[ Grunts. coughs ]
[ Whooshing ]
Aah!
[ Knife clatters ]
[ Bones snap ]
Aah!
[ Grunting ]
[ Groans ]
The Darkness --
what do you know?
Okay.
So I misjudged.
You're not scared.
You're mad.
And I get it.
I mean. it must suck
being everyone's tool.
manipulated and used
by the angels.
by your enemies.
by your friends.
Aah!
♪
You thought if you
could get your Grace back.
it would help fix you.
but it hasn't!
Oh! Aah!
The Darkness.
[ Bones crunching ]
[ Choking ] Why. Amara?
I thought we had
an understanding.
Yeah.
Your promise to protect me.
And. then. hours later.
I'm assaulted in my own room.
Well. you don't seem
terribly upset by it.
That's not the point.
I've decided I don't need
your protection.
and I certainly don't need
your captivity.
Aah.
I'm done.
[ Grunting ]
You trying out some kind
of no-kill policy?
Who do you have to thank
for how angry you are.
how lost?
Aah!
[ Breathing heavily ]
You're welcome.
[ Grunting ]
Oh. a hunter.
You of all people should know
pacifism doesn't pay.
[ Groaning ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Crackling ]
Aah!
[ Grunting ]
[ Breathing heavily ]
Go on. Castiel.
End me.
[ Grunts ]
[ Breathing heavily ]
No.
All right.
Two out of three.
Aah!
Sam: Dean?!
[ Pounding on door ]
[ Whooshes ]
Oh!
Dean!
[ Grunting ]
[ Whooshing ]
Aah!
[ Gasping ]
It's time -- time for you
to blink your tired ass
back to your throne
and lick your wounds.
I'll spare your life
on one condition.
Safe passage for Dean
out of here after I've gone.
Yes!
[ Whooshes ]
Ah!
[ Panting ]
Good.
Now...
Get out of my room.
Oh. please. Castiel.
Help me.
You said you were happy.
your "bootstraps."
I was faking it.
I mean. I thought.
"how -- how hard could it be?"
You won't.
You can't.
Can't take any more --
not a single human day.
[ Sobbing ] I mean...
The indignities --
they just don't stop --
make--
making my rent and keeping
my phone charged...
Hemorrhoids.
You were right.
Metatron.
I am sick
of having my strings pulled.
which is why I won't let you
manipulate me
into letting you off easy.
[ Sobs ]
Tell me about
the Darkness.
Tell me. what is
happening here between us?
You save me. I save you.
What?
You were the first thing I saw
when I was freed.
and it had been so long.
Maybe that's it --
my first experience
of his creation.
You can't help
but represent that for me --
the sweet triumph
and the even sweeter folly
of what he's wrought.
There's no fighting it.
I'm fascinated.
The truth -- ha --
it'd make the Bible thumper''
heads explode.
[ Sniffles ]
I mean.
they want their God
to be a-a f-finger-snapping.
all-powerful creator.
you know...
And they want magic...
Mary Poppins.
But what he did --
creation...
that took work.
Took sacrifice.
In order
to create the world.
God had to give up
the only thing
he'd ever known.
He had to betray and sacrifice
his only kin.
The Darkness...
His sister.
It's been great
seeing you again. Dean.
but it's time
for me to go.
There's a whole world out there
for me to explore.
and I can
practically taste it.
Soon. I'll be strong enough
to do what I came here to do.
What's that?
Settle an old score --
the oldest score.
Told you.
Oh!
[ Grunts ]
[ Groans ]
Look. guys.
I'm as glad as anyone
that Stella got
her groove back. okay?
But you let Metatron go?
Dean. how many times are you
gonna repeat that question?
I'm gonna say it again.
You let Metatron go!
He's not going anywhere.
If he makes a move. if he draws
the slightest attention.
the full force of angelkind
will snuff him out.
Look. you --
neither of you saw him.
He is a human.
and a pitiable one at that.
He's not a threat to us.
I-I mean.
I put him in traction.
Guys.
bigger fish to fry here.
Amara is in the wind.
Yeah.
God's freaking sister.
You said you were close.
Dean.
how'd she get away?
I'm sorry. what part of
"God's freaking sister"
did you not understand?
She overpowered me --
end of story.
What's our plan here.
fellas?
You said you got everything you could
out of Metatron. right?
So. where on earth
are we gonna find an answer
on how to stop her?
I don't suppose God's decided
to share any wisdom on the matter.
I'll look into the lore.
♪
[ Thunder crashing ]
[ Breathing heavily ]
♪ Girl ♪
♪ you'll be a woman soon ♪
♪ I love you so much.
can't count all the ways ♪
♪ I've died for you. girl.
and all they can say is ♪
♪ "he's not your kind" ♪
♪ they never get tired
of putting me down ♪
♪ and I never know
when I come around ♪
♪ what I'm gonna find ♪
♪ don't let them make up
your mind ♪
♪ don't you know. girl ♪
♪ you'll be a woman soon ♪
♪ please ♪
♪ come take my hand ♪
♪ girl ♪
♪ you'll be a woman soon ♪
♪ soon ♪
♪ you'll need a man ♪
== sync. corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm